[
  {
    "questionNo": "1",
    "question": "How are you?",
    "answers": ["Good", "Bad", "Horny", "Modi"],
    "correctAns": "Good",
    "subject": "English",
    "topic": "Grammer"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "2",
    "question": "question2",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op1",
    "subject": "English"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "5",
    "question": "Math",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op1",
    "subject": "Math"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "5",
    "question": "Science",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op2",
    "subject": "Science"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "5",
    "question": "Geog",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op4",
    "subject": "Geog"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "5",
    "question": "Math5",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op3",
    "subject": "Math"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "5",
    "question": "Math6",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op3",
    "subject": "Math"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "6",
    "question": "Math2",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op3",
    "subject": "Math"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "7",
    "question": "Math3",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op3",
    "subject": "Math"
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "8",
    "question": "Math4",
    "answers": ["op1", "op2", "op3", "op4"],
    "correctAns": "op3",
    "subject": "Math"
  }
]
